<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chicago Bears Quizzler</string>

    <string name="true_button">True</string>
    <string name="false_button">False</string>
    <string name="initial_score">Score 0/46</string>

    <string name="incorrect_toast">Wrong!</string>
    <string name="correct_toast">Correct!</string>

    <string name="question_1">Former Chicago Bears quarterback Jay Cutler wore the number 6 on his jersey.</string>
    <string name="question_2">Running back Walter Payton had the nickname "Sweetness".</string>
    <string name="question_3">The last Super Bowl appearance for the Chicago Bears was during the 2005&#8211;2006 season.</string>
    <string name="question_4">Former Chicago Bears wide receiver and first round pick David Terrell wore 83 on his jersey.</string>
    <string name="question_5">Running back Matt Forte is the current all-time leader in rushing yards for the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_6">Quarterback George Halas wore the number 3 on his jersey.</string>
    <string name="question_7">Former Chicago Bears wide receiver Brandon Marshall set the all-time team record in receptions in 2012.</string>
    <string name="question_8">The Chicago Bears traded wide receiver Marty Booker for Miami Dolphins defensive end Adewale Ogunleye in 2005.</string>
    <string name="question_9">Kicker Kevin Butler is the all-time scoring leader for the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_10">Defensive lineman Dan Hampton is the all-time sack leader for the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_11">Quarterback Sid Luckman is the all-time passing yards leader for the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_12">Return specialist Devin Hester was drafted in 4th round of the 2006 NFL Draft.</string>
    <string name="question_13">Former Chicago Bears running back Anthony Thomas won the Offensive Rookie of the Year award in 2001.</string>
    <string name="question_14">Former Chicago Bears wide receiver Alshon Jeffrey was drafted in the 3rd round of the 2011 NFL Draft.</string>
    <string name="question_15">Former Chicago Bears center Olin Kreutz wore the number 58 on his jersey.</string>
    <string name="question_16">The Chicago Bears finished the regular season 15&#8211;1 and during their 1985 Super Bowl winning season.</string>
    <string name="question_17">Defensive lineman Steve McMichael is the all-time career leader in tackles for the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_18">Former head coach Lovie Smith lead the Bears to a 12&#8211;4 record in 2006 during their Super Bowl losing season.</string>
    <string name="question_19">Former head coach Mike Ditka was also an offensive lineman for the Chicago Bears before his coaching career.</string>
    <string name="question_20">Linebacker Brian Urlacher was a former 1st round draft pick for the Chicago Bears in 2000.</string>
    <string name="question_21">Defensive end Richard Dent had the nickname Mongo while playing for the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_22">Punter Adam Podlesh was the punter for the Chicago Bears during the 2005 season.</string>
    <string name="question_23">Kicker Robbie Gould was the kicker for the Chicago Bears during the 2005 season.</string>
    <string name="question_24">Guard Kyle Long made the pro bowl during his rookie season.</string>
    <string name="question_25">Wilbur Marshall was a starting linebacker for the Chicago Bears during the 1985 Super Bowl winning season.</string>
    <string name="question_26">Chicago Bears quarterback Mitchell Trubisky was the third overall pick during the 2017 NFL Draft.</string>
    <string name="question_27">Chicago Bears running back Tarik Cohen was drafted in the 6th round of the 2017 NFL Draft.</string>
    <string name="question_28">Doug Flutie played for the Chicago Bears as a quarterback.</string>
    <string name="question_29">Cornerback Charles Tillman wore the number 35 on his jersey.</string>
    <string name="question_30">Cornerback Nathan Vasher returned a missed field goal against the San Francisco 49ers for 108 yards.</string>
    <string name="question_31">As of 2019, the number 54 on a jersey is officially retired from being a jersey number.</string>
    <string name="question_32">Linebacker Dick Butkus wore the number 56 on his jersey.</string>
    <string name="question_33">The Chicago Bears defeated the Seattle Seahawks during the divisional round of the playoffs in 2010.</string>
    <string name="question_34">Former Chicago Bears quarterback Jim Miller wore the number 12 on his jersey.</string>
    <string name="question_35">Former Chicago Bears long snapper Patrick Mannelly has the team record for most games played with 245 games.</string>
    <string name="question_36">Running back Thomas Jones had three 1000+ yard seasons while with the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_37">Quarterback Sid Luckman is the all-time leader in interceptions thrown while playing with the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_38">Cornerback Charles Tillman is the all-time leader in forced fumbles while playing with the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_39">The Chicago Bears won the NFL Championship in 1948 against the New York Giants.</string>
    <string name="question_40">The Chicago Bears selected tight end Greg Olsen in the 2nd round of the 2007 NFL Draft.</string>
    <string name="question_41">Michael Burton was a backup guard who played for the Chicago Bears during the 2018 season.</string>
    <string name="question_42">Running back Walter Payton rushed for 16,726 yards during his career with the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_43">Running back Gale Sayers rushed for 8,989 yard during his career with the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_44">Running back Neal Anderson is all-time leader in rushing touchdowns for the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_45">James "Big Cat" Williams played 166 games in his career, all with the Chicago Bears.</string>
    <string name="question_46">Alan Page is a Hall of Fame defensive tackle who played the majority of his career with the Chicago Bears.</string>
</resources>
